♪ In the not-to-distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday A.D. ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ Then we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot Roll Call ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
♪ Tom Servo ♪
♪ Croooow! ♪
♪ You're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
- I know, I know.
Hi, everybody. Welcome
to the Satellite of Love.
Gypsy's feeling king of
depressed today, you know.
A lot of people
don't realize this
but she has a lot of
responsibilities on the ship.
- Yeah, like we don't have any.
- Hey now, listen,
you guys, you know,
she's the one who keeps a
lot of the higher system
functions running on the ship
so you guys can gallivant
around, all right?
That's why sometimes she's
kinda hard to understand.
- Yeah, that's why she
sounds like Moms Mabley.
(Crow and Servo laugh)
- That's great.
Now listen, you guys.
I'm gonna have to ask Gypsy
to shut down some of the higher
functions she's been slaving
so she can free up her mind
and tell me what's bugging her.
Now I need...
Now I need you to...
Now would you guys look at
me when I'm talking to you?
All right, now I'm
gonna need you guys
to finally do some work around
here for a change, capisce?
- [Computer] Commercial
sign in 15 seconds.
- Now Tom Servo,
I want you to go down
to the Maneuvering Room
and keep those heat shields
pointed towards the sun.
Crow,
I need you to do
everything else, all right?
And stay frosty, you two.
- Cool.
- Check.
- [Computer] Commercial
sign in five,
four, three, two...
Commercial sign now.
- We'll be right back.
- And so, I guess I'm just
feeling the old ennui, you know.
It's nothing, I'm just
a little depressed.
Look, you're busy.
We'll talk about this later.
I'll re-initiate the astronic
and photonic systems on my mark.
Re-initiate!
(Joel coughs)
- Thanks, Gypsy.
I'm real glad we could
have this little talk.
- Richard Basehart!
- Right, Richard
Basehart, that's right.
- Howdy, Cap'n!
- Hey, stud!
- You know, I had the
nicest talk with Gypsy.
She's a really warm
and wonderful person.
- Uh, Joel, the
scientists are calling.
- Yeah, I just feel like
she's my new best friend.
I can't even describe it.
- Well don't try 'cause
the scientists are calling.
- Oh, okay.
- No, Joel, the
button's over there.
- I'll get it.
- [Servo] For crying out loud.
- Oh, hello, Joel-erini Weenie!
Is that funny, Frank?
Have we used that one before?
- Uh, no.
- Well, Joel, it's time
for the invention exchange.
You may wonder why
we're dressed this way.
- I wonder.
- Shut up.
We're dressed this way because
I've lost my train of thought
and don't you ever interrupt
me when I'm on a roll again!
- [Both] We're dressed
this way because of the...
- Anyway, Joel, as you know,
children have long looked up
to cowboys as role models.
And vice-versa.
That's where we get
the hobby horse from.
But today kids are looking
for more sophisticated
role models.
What's that thing, Frank?
- Kookoo kids lookin'
for kookoo kicks.
(clucks goofily)
- Yeah, anyway.
- So what we've done,
and since today's movie
is kind of a biker movie,
what we've done is we've taken
the whole hobby horse concept,
we've pared it down a bit,
shot some paint on it.
And what we have here is the...
the Hobby Hog!
Woo!
(engines revving)
- That's right!
It's for kids who want to
get into concert security!
But we haven't forgot the child!
The saddlebags are
filled with zwieback
and the tank's
filled with Bosco!
Kick it down, mamma jamma!
(engines rev)
- Hey, I'm sorry,
I wasn't listening.
Cambot, could you bring
it out a little bit?
All right, there's nothing
the fellas and me enjoy more
than a big, juicy, sloppy pizza
before we head on
in for an experiment
in the Mystery Science Theater.
Anyway, this is a
thing I invented.
It kinda puts a high-tech
spin on an old standard.
It's the 3D pizza.
I based it on the
premise of the 3D chess
from the old Star Trek show.
- It's even better
with the 3D glasses on.
I feel like I'm really here!
- Let's see, uh...
Pepperoni to
anchovy, level four.
Check!
I've got you now, Mr. Bond!
- And if you've got extra,
you can take and use this neat
pizza lunch box I invented
and carry it right into the
Mystery Science Theater.
- Joel, that's a trash can lid.
- Oh.
Well, you can use
it for that, too.
What do you think, sirs?
- I'm sorry, Joel,
we couldn't hear you!
Your experiment today
is called Wild Rebels.
- It's a cool,
swingin', heavy trip.
(clucks goofily)
- What is that noise?
- It's just a sound, that's all.
- I know, but you
do it all the time.
- It's nothing really.
- What does it mean?
It's about me, isn't it?
- No.
(alarms buzzing)
- [All] We've got movie sign!
♪ Wild Rebels ♪
♪ We're reckless ♪
- [Servo] I wish I could eat
pizza, Joel, that looks good.
- [Joel] Steve Lame-o.
- [Crow] Hey, Pastrano!
My favorite sammich.
- [Servo] And the
Glaucoma Players.
Boy, I can hardly read
this, how about you?
- [Joel] There's no way
we can read 'em all.
And here's the people with
the really bad agents.
- [Servo] That's impossible.
- [Crow] Catchy tune.
- [Servo] Okay, is
that better or worse?
- [Joel] That's a little better.
- [Servo] That's
gotta be better.
How about this?
- [Joel] That's worse.
- [Servo] Better
one, better two?
- [Joel] Better one.
- [Servo] Okay, good.
- [Crow] Comet Pictures,
a real flash in the pan.
- [Joel] What's the extra E for?
- [Crow] Well that's for extra--
- [Servo] (coughing) Ixnay.
- [Crow] I'll tell you later.
(siren blaring)
- [Servo] Trouble with the car?
- [Joel] I'm here, Steve.
- Tough break, Rod.
- [Servo] That's Rod.
- Man, it's not the work.
- [Joel] I don't think
the scene's over yet, Rod.
- There goes two
years of saving.
- [Servo] Well you
shouldn't carry cash
in the glove compartment, Rod.
- Nothing.
- Come on, Rod, you can
build another super.
- What?
Chewing gum and spit?
- [Servo] No thanks, I just ate.
- [Crow] By the way,
who are you anyway?
- I wanna call it quits.
- Hey, Rod, it's
all in the game!
- [Crow] And who are you?
- Some game.
- [Joel] Paint your house.
- [Servo] How's my
sandwich coming?
- [Crow] Geez,
what a lousy day...
What?
What? What do you want from me?
- [Servo] Down the
trail of shame he goes.
- [Crow] Hippity hop.
More like dragitty drag.
Poor guy.
Uh, oh.
Here comes the sermon
on the Gran Turino.
- Everybody!
- [Joel] Blessed are
the grease monkeys,
for they will lube...
(Crow and Servo mimic grumbling)
- [Servo] Wrap around here,
get in the shot, everybody.
- [Joel] Gotta stay on camera.
Hi, my name's Rod
and I'm a gasaholic.
- [Crow And Servo] Hi, Rod!
- This is an official auction.
I got a new trailer over there.
- [Joel] Hey, nice guitar.
- Brand new tires and rims.
What am I bid for it?
- [Crow] Well I'll
take the guit--
- [All] Huh?
- Come on, don't be
bashful, what am I bid?
They're brand new.
- Come on down from there, Rod.
You don't want to sell out.
- [Servo] I made
this movie, didn't I?
- I've had it.
- [Servo] How about these
Robert Culp I Spy pants?
- Thousand dollar
rig, brand new.
- Hundred dollars.
- You sure you can
afford it, man?
- [Joel] Okay, I
can't, dickweed!
- That's all right,
man, forget it.
- [Crow] How about if I throw
in dinner and a movie with me?
- [Servo] Twenty dollars.
- Two fifty.
- All right, two fifty.
Do I hear three?
- Four hundred!
- [Servo] Bid four,
bid four fifty.
- It's worth more.
- [Joel] Because I love you!
- Four twenty-five!
- Bless your stingy little hard.
- [Joel] What does
he mean by that?
- All right.
Four seventy-five.
- [Servo] Well, that tops me.
You sold it to yourself, Rod.
- [Crow] What an idiot.
- Do I hear five, four fifty?
Do I hear five?
- [Crow] Now you're
embarrassing them, Rod.
- [Joel] Alienation.
- Four seventy-five.
All right, four fifty once.
That's it, huh?
- [Servo] Poor stupid dope.
- Four fifty once.
- [Joel] Mm-hm, mm-hm.
Yeah, yeah, keep going.
- Four fifty twice.
- [Joel] Four fifty
three times a lady.
- All right, sold to my
good friend Walt Simpson
for 450 United States dollars.
- [Crow] Hey, did it tell
ya I was biddin' in pesos?
Here's your dollar!
- [Joel] Get off that
Batmobile, creep.
- [Crow] Look at that dent.
- [Servo] Look at the body
we have to do on that now.
- You bought it fair
and square for $450
and that's all I'm gonna take.
- [Servo] That's all
I'm gonna give ya!
- Four hundred and fifty.
Count it.
- I trust ya, man.
- [All] Sucker!
- What are your plans?
- [Crow] Get off this film.
- I haven't got any.
I'll just shove off.
- [Joel] Shove off...
Oh, I know what you're saying.
There's my guitar at least.
Huh?
Oh, there it is.
- Well, old buddy,
take care of yourself.
- [Joel] Let me outta here!
I'm a ventriloquist
dummy in this bag!
Please, help me!
- [Servo] Darn fool.
Hey!
- [All] All right, yeah!
- [Servo] Looks like
some local color there.
- [Crow] Yeah, white trash.
- [Joel] Hey, those guys are
marked clearly as poison.
Don't eat 'em.
- [Servo] If you take
these bikers internally,
do not induce vomiting.
- [Crow] No, the movie
will do that for you.
It's like an ipecac.
- [Joel] An ipa...
Oh, that Genesis album?
- [Servo] Hey, Tommy Lasorda.
Thanks for the
ride, Mr. Lasorda.
- [Joel] Now remember,
just one delicious
shake in the morning
and lunch and a
sensible meal after.
- [Servo] Whatever,
thanks for the ride.
Good luck with the football
team or whatever it is you do.
- Thanks for the ride, man.
- [Servo] Yeah, now scram.
Hm, that's pretty neat.
- [Joel] Kind of an
open concept place.
One of these, huh?
Kinda funny.
This one looks like
it's made out of rubber.
- [Servo] What do you know?
- [Joel] Go figure.
What's this over here?
- [Servo] Looks like it
says "Kiss Me, I'm Irish".
Who'd know?
- [Crow] Oh, would you just
get in the door, please?
- [Joel] Kinda like the back
yard of the Brady Bunch house.
- [Servo] Whoa!
- [Crow] Hey, good thing
we got a wide screen.
- [Servo] Ronald McDonald
shaking his McBooty.
Woo-hoo!
- [Crow] Yeah, I wonder
what they're makin'
new butts out of this year.
- [Servo] One, two, cha-cha-cha.
One, two, cha-cha-cha.
- [Joel] Hmm...
Well, I'm not too
sure but it's possible
I just might be a little
too hip for this room.
Let's just see.
- [Servo] I doubt it.
Wild Rebels cha-cha.
- [Crow] Hey, look!
They turned the flying sub
from the Voyage to the Bottom
of the Sea show into a bar!
- [Gypsy] Richard Basehart?
- [Joel] No, Gypsy, sorry.
(Gypsy groans)
Poor girl. (tisks)
- Just come to town?
- Just passing through.
- Beautiful guitar you got.
Can you play blues?
- [Servo] Oh, just
'cause I'm white,
you think I can play the blues!
- What'll you have?
- Lemme have a beer.
- Okay, what kind?
- Cold.
- [Crow] Now remind
me to hit you later.
- [Joel] What are those
three guys doing anyway?
- [Servo] I dunno, it's kinda...
- [All] Whoa!
- [Servo] Where'd she come from?
- [Crow] Sorry it got
warm as I brought it over.
- Okay?
- [Crow] Jerk.
- Jeeter.
Jeeter.
Dig the cat at the bar.
The one with the gitso.
- [Servo] Hmm, ring
around the collar.
- [Joel] I really like you
but we could never wash our
clothes in the same load.
- Hi, handsome.
- [Crow] Say...
- What's he got,
leprosy or something?
- No.
He looks familiar,
real familiar.
- [Servo] Yeah, he was in
the first part of the film.
- Would you believe
Banjo's in love!
- [Crow] Okay, would you
believe mildly infatuated?
How about a schoolboy crush?
- Let's try dancing first.
- [Joel] Hey, keep
my beer cold, huh?
(rock band plays)
- [Crow] Would you like a
little pants with your belt?
- [Joel] Ladies and gentlemen,
from England, the Femtones!
- [Servo] Nice haircut, huh?
- [Crow] Nice vest.
- [All] My lunch goes (blecch)!
- [Servo] Oh, brother.
Joel, is this Catalina
Caper all over again?
- [Joel] I don't think so
but it's the same spirit.
(Crow and Servo belching)
- [All] My lunch goes (blecch)!
♪ Do I love her, yes I do ♪
♪ Of course she'll love me too ♪
♪ There are rules
I have to learn ♪
♪ Bridges I must burn ♪
♪ Can I do it ♪
♪ My heart says-- ♪
(belching)
- [Servo] Ladies and gentlemen,
please, for your
viewing enjoyment,
concentrate on the woman.
- [Crow] Yeah, try not
to listen to the music.
- [Servo] Don't look at
him, whatever you do.
- [Crow] Okay, I can
get you Bob Denver.
- [Joel] As a romantic
lead, I just don't see it.
- [Crow] Really.
I know the Gilligan's
Island thing typecast him
but you should see him dance.
- [Joel] You're always
tryin' to pawn off
your has-been TV talent on me.
Hold it, I got Bill
Bixby on line one.
The Press Agent sketch,
ladies and gentlemen.
- [Servo] Pretty good.
Nice job, guys.
- [Joel] Say...
Oh!
♪ And I will ♪
- [Servo] I will.
- [Servo] I will!
I will kill you!
- [Crow] Hey, how did
those guys do that?
How did they fade like that?
- [Servo] Amazing!
- [Joel] Hey, are you
guys wearing Toughskins?
- [Bartender]
Something for the lady?
- Yes, just a beer, that's all.
- [Crow] Cold.
- I got it.
You know who that cat is?
(Servo meows)
- I'm breathless.
Pray tell, who?
- That's Rod Tillman, man.
The hottest of
Detroit Iron Boys.
- [Servo] Oh, a Teamster.
- Real pusher behind that wheel.
- Stock car driver, huh?
How interesting.
- [Joel] But stupid.
- [Servo] Go hit on him.
Aren't these places phony?
I don't usually come here but...
- Sweetheart.
Go powder your nose.
- [Servo] Can I borrow a mirror?
- You heard the man, baby, blow!
- [Servo] You want me to blow
or do you want me
to powder my nose?
- You gonna let these
creeps talk to me this way?
- [Joel] Uh, yeah.
- Look, I don't know what's
goin' on, but I don't like it.
- Sweetheart.
Crawl back into the woodwork
for the rest you are.
I don't wanna have to mess
up that pretty little face.
- [Servo] Oh, okay.
Oh, you're still talking to her.
- [Joel] Oh, this must be
taken on the new crotch cam.
- [Jeeter] Rod
Tillman, I presume.
- [Crow] Yes, Dr. Stanley.
- That's the name.
- We are avid fans of yours.
- [Crow] We like your
early funny stuff.
- Thanks.
It was fun while it lasted.
- Do I detect a note of
resentment in that statement?
- [Servo] Do I detect
a note of resentment
in that statement?
- You hard, baby, what happened?
Chicken begin to cackle?
- [Crow] Leave my
chicken out of this.
- No, man, the bread ran out.
- [Joel] Oh, so I couldn't
bread the chicken.
- Mr. Tillman, Banjo
meant no offense.
- Didn't sound that way to me.
- [Crow] Didn't smell
that way, either.
- The name is Rod.
- Of course, of course.
- [Joel] Grr.
- I'm Jeeter.
- [Servo] The fast land animal.
- Your friend over
here is Banjo.
- [Crow] He came from
Alabama on my knee.
- [Jeeter] And my gregarious
follower over here is Fats.
- [Joel] That's
self-explanatory.
- [Jeeter] And this is...
- [Joel] Hello, Betty!
- [Jeeter] Or I should
say that is Linda.
Cool it.
Cool it, man, cool it!
- [Servo] He's not worth it.
- Now, where was I?
- [Servo] I think you were
stinkin' up the joint.
- What are you
doing around here?
- [Servo] A little of
this, a little of that.
- [Joel] All right, take two.
- [Jeeter] Where
are you staying?
- Nowhere's enough.
- [Crow] Motel 6?
- Well then,
may I give you an invitation
to share our humble chateau?
- [Servo] Your hat?
- [Jeeter] It's not very much
but it's what we call home.
- [Joel] What you call
home, Rambo calls hell.
- My invitation was by no
means extended without reason.
You see, I have a business
proposition to offer you.
Which could mean a lotta bread
and an unlimited expense
account could be yours.
- [Servo] That means security
for you and your loved ones.
- Go ahead, I'm listening.
- This is not the
place nor the time.
Please accept my invitation
to share our humble pad.
- [Servo] Now is it
your pad or your hat?
- [Joel] Will I have to
sleep with the stinky guy?
- Fine.
Linda, baby!
Come here!
- [Joel] You rang?
(Joel growls deeply)
- [Jeeter] Baby, I want
you to meet Rod Tillman.
Rod, say hello to Linda.
- [Crow] You'll be playing
the first round together.
Your category is
world geography.
- Listen, baby,
take my bike and ride
Rod out to our chateau.
- [Servo] Now it's
a chateau again.
- Sure, Jeeter.
- [Joel] Hey, what gives?
- Well aren't you going with us?
- We have
a little unfinished
business to attend to.
- [Crow] Yeah, they got to
go past the La Bianca place.
(out-of-tune guitar chord plays)
- [Joel] Hey, you play
that as well as he does.
- [Crow] Nice guitar.
Not!
- [Joel] Hey, Rod, let
me out of this suitcase!
Please!
For God's sake, let me out!
- [Servo] Oh, I love
meeting new people.
Hey!
It's Jason on the action cam.
- [Linda] Yeah, hop on, baby.
Wango!
- [Crow] Ze tango!
- [Joel] You know, we
gotta find out a way
to sew up the copyright on
those Hell's Angels logos.
These are goin' nowhere.
- I think we oughta
teach those college
creeps a lesson.
- [Crow] Physics or trig?
- [Servo] No, semantical
philosophy, butthead.
- [Crow] Oh, metal shop.
(all laugh menacingly)
- [Joel] Hey, don't let
'em know we got beer, okay?
Be cool.
- [Crow] No, kill the band!
- Hey, creep!
- [Joel] Uh, it's Brandon.
- You talkin' to me?
- You and your friends are
the only creeps in this joint.
- What's going on?
- You enjoy your dance
with our little mama?
- [Servo] That was your mom?
- Look, I just danced with her.
There's no harm done.
- Hey, you don't dig!
Our little mama's
like a virgin goddess.
- [Crow] Well, sorta.
- And no creeps,
no creeps are
allowed to touch her.
- [Crow] Only union
members and their families.
- Hey, these cats are
really way out, aren't they?
- [Joel] They're
totally bonkers!
- Like I said,
there's no harm done.
- Oh, baby.
There's no harm done.
None physically.
Until now!
- [Servo] Check, please!
(grunting)
- [Crow] There's never
a waitress around
when you need one.
- [Servo] Definitely
not gonna tip them now.
(Joel laughing goofily)
- [Joel] Uh, shiny object.
I like it.
- [Servo] Ah! Let's
savor the moments.
- Are you gentlemen
ready for the road?
(Servo laughing goofily)
- Yeah, baby, yeah,
anything you say.
- [Crow] Do we tip 15 or 20%
on a rumble? (chuckles goofily)
- Banjo, baby, lead the way.
(Crow and Servo
laughing goofily)
- [Crow] Tickle, tickle.
Does that bug you?
(chuckles goofily)
- [Man] I want my mama.
- [Joel] We're here all
week, enjoy the buffet.
(laughing)
- [Servo] I like
my job too much.
- [Joel] That's the thing
about a job like this.
I never think I have
to go to work tomorrow.
I just love it that much.
- [Crow] Did we
remember to punch out?
I can't remember.
- [Servo] Ah, life.
(engine revving)
- [Joel] Artsy craftsy.
- [Servo] Wow, look at
all those books up there.
- [Crow] Yeah, Leaves of Grass.
- [Joel] Trump: The
Art of the Deal.
- [Servo] Mein Kampf.
- [Crow] The Essays
of Pat Buchanan.
- Bright lights bug me.
This makes everything
much more cozy.
- [Servo] So how long
have you been workin' on
the David Duke's
campaign, honey?
- [Crow] Whoa, those
trees are loud!
- [Servo] Yikes!
(engines revving)
- [Joel] Wow, it sure
is dark out, isn't it?!
- [Servo] Two roads
diverged into a yellow wood,
and sorry I could not
take my heart down both
and be one traveler,
long I stood.
- [Joel] You beat the
stuffing out of three preppies
and given away the girl,
but before the day is through,
you'll take enough
drugs to kill a horse.
Now it's Miller Time.
- [Crow] Guys, it doesn't
get any stupider than this.
- [Joel] Boy, you
know, it's really dark.
- [Servo] Really
dark. Boy, it it dark.
Pitch black out here,
I can't see a thing.
- [Joel] They got
their sunglasses on.
- [Servo] Must be a new moon.
I don't know, it's so dark.
- [Crow] Very
bright for darkness.
(Servo mimics kissing)
- [Servo] Boy, you taste
like Joseph Goebbels.
- Those three bosom buddies
of yours due here any minute,
I want this place
lit up like Broadway.
- [Crow] They say the neon
lights are brighter on Broadway.
- Fantastic.
- Three on one is not much fun.
- [Servo] Says you!
(Joel squeaking)
- [Joel] Orange cappuccino?
Swiss Mocha?
(Crow and Servo
mimic The Penguin)
(Servo sighs)
- [Servo] Celebrate the
moments of your life
with General Foods
International Ripple.
(gang laughs)
We better split, guys.
- [Crow] Okay.
(Servo laughs mockingly)
- [Joel] Oh, for fun!
- Gosh, Joel, that biker
guy sure is sleazy,
but, boy, what a vocabulary!
- Yeah, he's quite eloquent
for a piece of lowlife scum.
- Well you guys might
be surprised to find out
that a lot of the great
thinkers of this century
actually rode in
motorcycle gangs.
In fact I've got
a few drawings--
- Don't tell me.
You've prepared a presentation
using artist renderings.
- Right. You know, you
read me like a book.
And anybody who
reads a lot of books
will know who the
Algonquin Round Table was.
- Well of course.
Alexander Woollcott,
George S. Kaufman,
Robert Benchley, Dorothy Parker.
- Right. Well I've
got this drawing here.
Bring it in a
little bit, Cambot.
Here's the group,
here's their gang.
It's called Satan's Sardonics.
Now, these guys terrorized
the whole East Coast
until one day they were
unexpectedly wiped out
in a rumble with the
cast of What's My Line?
- [Crow] Wow, I guess
that Bennett Cerf
is tougher than people thought!
- [Joel] Yeah.
Now, when you think
of a tough macho rider
who writes in a tense,
hard-boiled style,
who do you think of?
- [Servo] Truman Capote?
- [Joel] Exactly!
See, his gang, Oscar's Wild
Ones, they were leather boys,
were all the range until
Norman Mailer's gang,
Hell's Egos,
mixed it up with
Gore Vidal's gang,
the Vital Sassoons.
- [Crow] Boy,
sounds pretty messy.
"If they don't look good,
we don't look good."
- [Joel] Yeah, there was gel
and mousse for miles around.
The carnage didn't end
until they all joined forces
and finally beat up
Dick Cavett.
- Well, at least we know
all that's in the past now.
- [Joel] Oh, no,
are you kidding?
The intelligentsia's duking it
out on Harleys more even now!
Yeah, sure, check it out.
Here's Ted Koppel's
gang right there.
They're called the Bloods.
Yeah, he's finally the
toughest of them all
'cause they're riding
with Stephen Hawking now.
They beat Bill Moyer's
gang, Moyer's Marauders,
even though Bill rode
with Joseph Campbell.
Everyone though Joseph
Campbell was tough
but that was just a myth.
- Joel, I hope you always
let us ride in your gang.
- Yeah, no problem.
Just so long as you don't
mess with my old lady.
- Oh, fight us off
with a stick, Joel!
(Gypsy cries)
- Oh, that's just great.
Crow, you know she's
especially sensitive right now.
- I'm sorry.
- Dickweed.
(gang members laughing)
- [Joel] So you see,
there really are a lot
of brilliant bikers.
- [Servo] It's amazing.
- [Crow] Like these guys.
(Servo slurps, belches)
- [Joel] You know, I feel
a little bit uncomfortable,
but I need to network.
- Nothing like a little
vino to soothe the palate
after a dusty rub.
- [Crow] And da wine
is good too, sir.
- [Joel] Uh, who's
gotta use da helmet?
(Servo laughs goofily)
- Hey, baby.
You remember that
little college banana
you were dancin' with?
- [Servo] Yeah, well
now he's a banana split
with nuts on top.
(Servo laughs goofily, hoots)
- He's missin'
his face. (laughs)
He's missin' his face!
- Now, Banjo.
Such talk will upset our guests.
- [Servo] Ah, room temperature.
- We want nothing
but pleasantries.
- [Crow] Who the hell
are you, Falstaff?
- Let's cut out all
these formalities
and lay the chips on the table.
What's happening?
- [Joel] I love you!
(Jeeter laughs)
- I like this guy,
I really like him.
- He's too square,
baby, a real square.
- Look, you just
keep tryin' to put
that square peg in a round hole
and everything will be fine!
- [Crow] What'd he mean by that?
- Peace.
If we're to be one
big happy family,
we must live in tranquility.
- [Servo] I love it
when he talks this way.
- Okay, Jeeter.
What do you want from me?
- Sit down, Rod.
Relax!
- [Crow] Set a spell,
take your shoes off.
(Servo mimics fart)
- As you might have surmised,
my happy little group
here is from California.
- [Joel] Stanford, right?
- We're strangers to this
Southern countryside.
We need a guide.
A chauffer, if you will.
To drive us around
this countryside
ever so swift.
- It smells.
- [Joel] You're the
stinky guy, right?
- Let Jeeter finish
his epilogue.
- [Crow] Well it's more
of a monologue, really.
- You're right, Rod.
We're bad.
Bad, bad people.
- [Servo] Does he mean
"bad bad" or "good bad"?
- [Crow] Sinbad.
- We do all sorts
of evil things.
- [Crow] We're
opening our own S&L.
- Real kicks!
- [Joel] Yeah, Lucky Charms.
- [Servo] And Honey Comb.
- They're very lucrative.
- Thanks but no thanks.
- Hey, let the man finish.
- [Crow] There's a whole
number he does at the end.
- We need you, man.
- [Joel] Join us.
- We need you real bad.
We're good on bikes,
but cars are a different tale.
- [Servo] Apparently,
they have more wheels on
them or something like that.
- The newspapers told the
story how ya got wiped out.
- [Crow] It's not out yet
but I'm heavily connected.
- Stocks for someone else,
you get peanuts!
- [Servo] But junk bonds, now
they're a different story.
- Bang!
One flameout and that's it.
But with us,
a couple of drives
and it's Moniesville
for a lifetime.
- [Joel] Plus good benefits,
medical, dental, 401(k).
Yeah, I could see
you in the future
with at least four chains on
your right shoulder alone.
- [Crow] Hey, there's
no smoking in here.
- Okay, what do you got in mind?
- An armored car...
- [Servo] An armadillo. (laughs)
- Just like the Roaring '20s.
- [Joel] Only many years later.
- None of that fancy
James Bond stuff.
No secret agent jazz.
Just plain old-fashioned guts.
You know, like Dillinger,
Pretty Boy Floyd...
- [Servo] Michael Milken,
Leona Helmsley, you know.
- What if I refuse?
- [Joel] Well, you get to keep
the girl as our gift to you.
- A lot of kicks, baby.
More kicks than I've
ever dreamed of.
- [Crow] So that
would be about four?
- One question:
what's with fat boy?
- [Servo] Aw, he's got
a thyroid condition.
He can't help his weight.
- The Big Kahuna of
the surfing pack.
And then one day
he got wiped out.
The board caught him
in back of the head.
He ain't never talked since.
- [Crow] Oh, the brains
of the operation.
- We love him just the same.
- [Joel] But he
can't love us back.
- Don't we, Fats?
- [Servo] Shouldn't have
had that Cobb salad.
- Gonna join us?
- [Joel] We're a fun group.
- [Servo] Join us.
- Sorry, friends.
But I like these clothes
and I'm not about to exchange
them for a suit of stripes.
- [Servo] But at
Foreman & Clark,
you can get a second
suit for just a dollar!
- Easy, baby.
- [Crow] Banjo, detune
your G-string, baby.
- Look, Rod.
- [Joel] He hasn't been the same
since the Nitty Gritty
Dirt Band broke up.
- Why all the pickin'
of the brains?
- [Joel] Well, I'm
starting my own company.
- I just wanted to find out
if your offer was legitimate.
- You gonna let him
get away with dis?
- [Crow] Are you
sure it wasn't Banjo
that got the board on
the back of the head?
- [Servo] No, he was
caught for six hours
in a transverse accident.
- I'm a very patient man.
- [Joel] But I hate bank lines.
They bug me.
- Well if that's all,
I guess I'll be going.
- [Servo] (clears throat)
Well, I had a great time.
You'll have to come to my
shotgun shack sometime.
Take care of your
head injuries, guys.
- [Crow] Let's exchange cards.
Contact my people.
- [Jeeter] Banjo, baby!
Where's your manners?
If this man wants
to go, let him.
- Please, baby.
- [Joel] I'll cut your
guitar, man, I will.
I'll cut you a new
sound hole, man.
- He can go!
- [Crow] Uh, well,
uh, thank you then.
It's, uh, been a pleasure.
(Crow chuckles
nervously, whines)
- [Joel] Well let me just say
I wish your business the best
and thanks for all the wine
and the use of your
chick and everything.
- [Crow] That's, uh...
That's the closet.
- [Servo] I hate
these curtains, man!
- Why'd you let
this guy get away--
- You let him in our house--
(mimicking grumbling)
- I said cool it!
- [Crow] What is this,
the McLaughlin Group?
- Our intentions,
not our plans.
- Why'd you let him go?!
- 'Cause he'll be back.
- [Servo] Got his keys. (laughs)
- Just give him a month.
No.
Two weeks.
When he gets hungry,
he'll be back.
- [Joel] Artsy craftsy!
- [Crow] Damn, what
was I thinkin'?
I'll never get a
second interview.
I should send them a
thank you letter though.
Note to myself:
never negotiate with bikers
hopped up on goofballs.
(trumpet sting)
It's showtime!
- [Man] Just hold
it right there.
- [Joel] We've got
Moog synthesizers!
We could kill you from here!
- [Detective] Now
raise your hands.
- [Servo] Now play
a G augmented.
Pat him down.
He's probably packin' a capo.
- He's clean, Lieutenant.
- [Crow] We're booking you
for impersonating Trini Lopez.
- What's your name, kid?
- [Joel] They call me Mr. Tibbs!
- Tillman.
Rod Tillman.
- What are you doin'
up in that cabin?
- [Servo] Oh,
networking, you know.
- I met some characters
at a dance and
they asked me to
come up so I went.
- Why'd you leave?
- [Crow] Lousy benefits.
- We didn't see eye-to-eye
on a few things.
- [Joel] And if they jumped
off a bridge, would you?
- What'd they want?
- Do you mind if I
put my hands down?
- No, that's fine, put 'em down.
- [Servo] Now put 'em
back up again! (laughs)
Didn't say Simon Says. Woo!
- [Joel] Hey, nice caboose.
- [Crow] So, what
you wanna hear?
Melancholy Baby?
Maybe at Sunset?
- Yeah, that sounds good.
- [Servo] Bavarian mint?
You can keep the mug.
- What did they want you for?
- [Joel] Got any of those
little finger sandwiches?
I'm starved.
- I should say an
ex-stock car driver.
And it seems that they
needed a wheel man.
- They're smart.
Real smart.
- [Joel] Yep.
- They know we can spot those
motorcycles before a robbery,
so now they're gonna
switch to a car.
- [Servo] Yeah, cars
are harder to see.
- If you know they're stealin',
why don't you arrest them?
- We have.
No witnesses, no evidence.
- [Joel] No jail, no
handcuffs, nothin'.
- How come?
- Well as I say,
they're smart.
They get rid of their
guns after each job.
- [Servo] Oh, look, they're
just really smart, okay?
- They certainly don't live big.
It's almost as though they're
robbin' just for
the thrill of it.
- Kicks.
Only for kicks.
- What'd you say?
- [Joel] It's a cereal, man!
Really good!
- They're only in it for kicks!
- Do you think you could
gain their confidence?
- [Crow] Look, you're
not a real cop, are you?
- Let's say that we didn't
leave the best of friends.
- Did they seem...
- [Joel] Smart?
- Disappointed when you
wouldn't drive for them?
- [Servo] They're really
close to the breast.
- Yeah, I think they
needed me real bad.
- [Crow] They cried.
- Look, Rod, I got a plan.
Now, if it works out,
would you be willin' to work
for us, work for the police?
- [Servo] (gasps)
If you'd have me!
- [Joel] It's called
Operation Weasel Snitch.
- Maybe.
Tell me more.
- [Servo] Lieutenant,
you have lovely feet!
- [Crow] It's Joe Namath!
Oh. No.
- [Joel] Oh no,
it's Marsha Brady,
all grown up and
back from college.
(Servo growls)
- [Crow] And she's wearing
her man's Van Heusen!
And he's wearing a beer.
(Joel snoring)
- [Servo] Oh, yikes, it
looks like Banjo exploded!
There's biker
shrapnel everywhere!
(sniffs)
Ooh! Whoa.
- [Joel] Uh, five
minutes, Mr. Manson!
- [Crow] No. No, mommy,
not the clown suit.
Well I'm glad to see someone's
getting a jump on the day.
- [Servo] Let's
take a look here.
Hm, Anaconda's up
three and a half.
American Can down a point.
Oh, look at this.
Zach Norman as
Sammy in Chief Zabu?
- [Joel] Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
- [Servo] Ah, that's better.
(engine revving)
- [Crow] Boss hog.
That's right, Fatty.
Seize the day.
- [Servo] Carpe diem.
Bording!
Ebbybody bup!
(crosstalk)
Rise and shine!
- [Joel] The milk man's heen!
- [Servo] Eardy
dird gets da durm!
(Fats yells)
Ebbybody up! Rise and shine!
- [Joel] What is it, boy?
Huh? What do you see?
- [Crow] Legs Diamond
got an excellent review!
(Servo mumbles incoherently)
- [Crow] The Lockhorns
wife burns a dinner?
Husband gets drunk?
I've seen it.
- How interesting.
- [Servo] Let me
see here, it's...
Oh, I forgot, I can't read.
- You just lost ten.
- Are going to the races?
- [Joel] No, we're
going to Disneyland.
- We're going to the races.
I wouldn't miss
that for anything.
- [Servo] Unless I die.
- [Joel] But first let's
look at some footage
from some of the great
races of yesteryear!
This 1951 race...
- [Announcer] ...triggered
a series of spins.
The cars attempt to weave
their way through the pack.
One car lost a wheel
in what appears to be a
survival of the fittest!
- [Servo] But is really not.
- [Crow] Hey, the
wheel's winning!
Get back on the track!
- [Servo] Where are they going?
- [Announcer] Car number
one is over the wall.
That's Buck Shepperton
over the east wall.
- [Crow] But it's far
too expensive to show us.
- [Announcer] Looks like
Buck is pinned in his car.
It appears it will take a
torch to free Buck Shepperton.
- [Joel] Or a really
good pair of scissors
or maybe one of those
hog head droppers
they use in the meat
packing industry.
- [Servo] Boy, that
announcer's really smart.
- [Crow] A few nose
donuts. (chuckles)
- [Joel] Hey, what are
you lookin' at, jerk?
- [Servo] Kids are just
too damn smart these days.
- [Joel] Hi, Rod!
Remember, you're undercover!
Don't talk to anybody!
- [Servo] Shh!
- Everything okay?
- Everything's
ready, Lieutenant.
- [Crow] Don't call me that.
- Good. Rod's been briefed.
- [Joel] And we pantsed him.
- Make him look good, Dutch.
- Will do, Lieutenant.
- Good luck.
- [Crow] Forget I ever met you.
- [Servo] I love you.
Nice caboose there, huh?
He's smart, too.
- [Joel] I don't
like this place.
Gives me the willies.
Hey, look, it's Mount Rushmore.
- [Servo] Mount Trashmore.
(Servo humming)
- [Announcer] After
a brief retirement,
Rod Tillman returns here to the
speedway in a new number 57.
- [Servo] Old Blue Eyes is back.
- [Announcer] ...if he
can regain that old form.
Many racing fans will remember
how Rod narrowly
escaped death...
- [Crow] Gimme that!
- [Servo] Oh, that's not nice.
- [Joel] Hey,
don't say hi. Geez.
- [Crow] Well, the driver
is missing or he's gone.
- [Servo] Bubblehead.
- [Joel] Two Nobel Prize
winners and a Pulitzer.
- [Announcer] Cars are
now ready for the start
of this 100-mile main event.
- [Crow] Hey, wait
until he says go!
(engines rumbling)
- [Announcer] Well,
the starter is running.
And off they go now on that
warmup lap getting into place.
(mimicking engines)
- [Announcer] And off they go!
All speed records should
be shattered today!
- [Joel] Along with
a couple of knees,
some femurs and
some skulls, too.
(mimicking engines)
(tires screeching)
- [Crow] Hey, you got a
little thing on your--
- [Servo] Right
there on the... yeah.
Whoa, what happened?
- [Crow] That looks like a
shootin' Tungsten out there.
- [Joel] It's the green cam!
- [Crow] For those of
you watching at home,
we have no idea what
the hell is goin' on!
- [Servo] It's an average
day out here on the A1A,
going up the coast.
(mimicking engines)
- [Joel] Grazin' in
the grass is a gas.
Baby, can you dig it!
- [Servo] So, who's
girl is she today?
Ah, looks like Banjo's.
- [Announcer] Car
number 57, Rod Tillman,
is still having a rough
time out there on the track.
(mimicking engines)
- [Servo] Whoa!
- [Announcer] He's
off to the side!
57 seems to be out...
No, he's all right.
Yes, he's back on the track.
- [Crow] Unfortunately,
he's all right.
- [Joel] Did anybody see that
Tom Cruise film this summer?
- [Servo] No.
Eat it, boy, eat it!
- [Crow] I have the worst luck!
- [Servo] Boy...
- [Joel] Get outta
there! Come on!
It's gonna blow! Come on!
- [Servo] Take my hand!
- [Announcer] He
appears to be okay.
- [Crow] How fortunate! This
will simplify everything!
(Servo laughs)
Hot car in the old Rod tonight.
- [Servo] You bet.
(siren blares)
- [Joel] That was fun.
What a day.
- [Servo] I love it.
- [Joel] Yeah, crown me fool.
Crown me fool.
Everybody line up and
take a big, steam--
(Servo clears throat)
- [Servo] Thank you, sir.
Merry Christmas.
So...
- [Joel] Gee, Wally!
- Tough luck, baby.
- [Crow] It's Dondi.
- Yeah, tough luck.
What are you guys
doin' here anyway?
- We thought maybe you'd like to
reconsider.
- [Servo] Uh-uh, no way I'm
gonna be in a dumb biker film.
(Crow coughs)
- I've had racing up to here.
I'm sick and tired of
every grease monkey
who can climb behind a
wheel runnin' me over.
Is your
offer still open?
- I think something
can be worked out.
- [Crow] Fatty,
get the surfboard.
- [Servo] We'll get you on
medical and dental right away.
- Let's split, man.
- Okay, I'm with you.
- [Joel] Think they're
talking about his head?
- [Servo] We gotta scram out.
- [Joel] Give a
hoot, don't pollute.
- [Crow] Can't watch that.
- For Rod's sake, I hope so.
- We'll be right back after
this important message.
Let's go.
- [Servo] Get the
box and ready, cue!
- Hey kids!
(funky bass line)
- One, two.
One, two, three.
♪ We're wild rebels ♪
♪ Crunchy fruity rebels ♪
♪ Pouring milk on them is
like shooting off a gun ♪
- It's Wild Rebels cereal,
the nutritious cereal.
It's like getting hit
in back of the head
with a surfboard of flavor!
- Look, marshmallow Fattys!
- Sugary Lindas!
- I got tangy twangy Banjos!
- Crunchy oat Rods!
- And Jeeters, too!
Die, Jeeter, die!
- [Mom] Kids?
What are you doing in there?
- Having a good breakfast, Mom!
- Pour on the milk!
One, two.
One, two, three, four.
♪ Wild Rebels ♪
♪ Funchy crunchy rebels ♪
♪ Don't bust your teeth ♪
♪ On something sweet and hard ♪
- Wild Rebels cereal, part
of this complete breakfast.
- Hey, there's a
cheap surprise inside!
- I got a gun!
- I got a sawed off pool
cue with a leather strap!
- I got a chunk of hose
filled with lead shot!
- All right, let's take it home!
♪ They won't get
soft or squishy ♪
♪ Better eat 'em
or you're a sissy ♪
♪ Just pound 'em down,
you stupid clown ♪
♪ They wild ♪
- Wild Rebels
cereal. Just eat 'em.
(alarms buzzing)
We got movie sign!
Wow, fruity kooky pebbles.
- [Servo] Mm-hmm, nutty.
- [Crow] Hey, they're
going to the turd museum!
- [Servo] World's largest.
- [Crow] Ride 'em.
- Remember, baby,
don't signal us until
he's beddie-bye.
- Don't sweat it,
I know what to do.
- [Crow] What does she
have a babysitting job?
They gonna knock
over a preschool?
Geez.
- [Joel] He's so
strong, I love him.
- [Servo] Hey, hey,
the car's mo...
Oh.
Hi, welcome to the 12th century!
- [Joel] Is this
Bruce Wayne's house?
Say, he's not bad!
Oh, that's me.
Excuse me.
- [Servo] Are they
robbing a bait shop?
- [Crow] Hmm, Winchester 408,
200-grain bullet with 2400 feet
per second muzzle velocity,
and an incredibly
fragged trajectory.
High powered rifle. Like.
- [Joel] This must
be where the South
bought all the stuff
for the Civil War.
- [Servo] And the
Spanish-American War
and the War of 1812.
- [Crow] Oh, Paul, have you
ever robbed a bait shop?
- [Joel] Ah, I don't
think so, Dave.
- Good morning, may I help you?
- Why, yes you may.
We've been bothered
by prowlers lately.
And with my husband
out of town...
- [Servo] (laughs) Nothing
like the wily charms
of an attractive woman to
get an old man off his guard.
- With all the unsavory
people in the world today,
you need protection.
- [Crow] Yes, yes, yes!
- What kind of gun
did you have in mind?
- I'm going to leave
that 100% up to you.
- [Joel] Wow, check out the
Ray Kroc death mask up there.
- [Servo] Now, this is the
one Ruby used to shoot Oswald.
- This is a very popular
model with the ladies.
- If you recommend it, I'm
sure it will suit my purpose.
Can you show me how it works?
- Surely.
- [Crow] Okay, stand
against that wall.
- You insert the clip.
Like this.
- [Servo] Thrusting it
manfully into the chamber.
- Like this.
See, this puts a bullet
up in the chamber.
Then all you have to
do is... (gun clicks)
pull the trigger.
Here, you try it.
- [Crow] Try it on me.
- This is the safety.
- I see now.
You put on the safety.
Then pull the trigger.
- [Joel] Wrong!
- No, first you put in the clip.
- Oh, first the clip.
- You're putting
it in backwards.
Let me help you.
(Crow quivers)
- [Joel] Oh, wow.
- [Crow] What is this, a
Shed Spread commercial?
- I'll take it.
- That'll be 79.95,
plus tax.
- I'll need some bullets.
- [Servo] This is my
rifle, this is my gun.
One is for retail,
the other's for fun.
- [Crow] Yes, yes,
yes! She likes me!
She likes me, she's buying it!
Don't screw it up, okay, calm.
She's buying it!
(giggles, clears throat)
- I'll throw these in as
a gift from the house.
- [Servo] And you get
the sneaker phone too!
- Would you mind
loading the gun for me?
(Joel grimaces)
- How stupid of me.
- [Crow] He's
loading it. (quivers)
- [Joel] Very interesting.
- [Servo] Hogan!
- Relax.
- [Servo] Schultz!
- She's a born actress.
- [Crow] She's no Streep.
- She's performing.
- There we are.
Always remember to
keep the safety on.
- [Crow] And if you can't
remember, name it after me.
(laughs nervously)
A little gun shop joke.
- Let me get you a nice
box to wrap that in.
- [Servo] (clears throat) Crow?
- [Joel] I'd like to
return these bullets
to their original owner.
- First rule of gun safety.
You never point a gun at anyone.
- Not even if you're
going to rob them?
- [Servo] No, not
even you're go... huh?
- I beg your pardon?
- Just do what I tell you
and you'll live to tell your
wife this shocking experience.
- Now just a minute--
- [Joel] Sounds like she
shot him with a staple gun.
- [Servo] Banjo, quit
playing yourself!
Come on!
- [Joel] Man, I wish these
clowns would learn to wash.
They always play the
radio too loud, too.
- [Crow] I'll, uh...
I'll just wait here then, huh?
- [Servo] Yee-hoo!
- [Crow] Hey, he looks like
Michael Caine in Zulu Dawn!
- [Banjo] This place is
gonna make us righteous, man!
Look at it!
- Oh ho!
Wait'll you see what I've got!
- [Servo] Clean up in
aisle three, please.
- [Crow] Oh! Ouch!
Oh, you gotta be
careful doin' that.
- [Joel] We're gonna
need a car here.
(Fats chuckling maniacally)
(Servo mimicking laughter)
- [Servo] Let's watch as
Benny Hill buys a gun.
- [Joel] I love you.
I really love you.
- [Crow] Uh, they do
have bullets there.
- Hey, what do you got, Banjo?
- [Servo] It's
called a gun, dear.
(grunting)
- [Joel] You know, I think
he's funnier than Benny Hill.
- [Servo] Definitely.
- [Crow] Blue light
special on chromosomes.
Extra ones.
- Come on, let's go!
- Okay, come on,
let's get outta here!
- [Crow] Not the hat, it
makes you look stupid.
- Come on, let's go!
Move it, come on, let's go!
- [Joel] Come on, ten
items or less, let's go.
- [Servo] Well, at least
they're not concealed weapons.
They'd get in trouble for that.
A modest assortment.
- Banjo, Fats, get
some ammunition.
- [Crow] How they gonna remember
what kinda guns they got?
- [Servo] This is the movies,
Crow, bullets are bullets.
- Just relax, baby.
It'll only be a minute.
- We need bullets!
How are we gonna kill
anybody without 'em, huh?
- [Crow] Kind of a
pre-shooting shopping spree.
- [Servo] Looks like...
Lunch!
- [Joel] Red ones and red
ones and red ones and...
- [Crow] Love me...
Thank you very much.
Now I'm gonna have a peanut
butter and nana sandwich.
- [Joel] Wonder if he knows
London Bridge is Falling Down.
- [Servo] Yeah, and
The Girl from Ipanema.
- [Crow] Thank you, I call
that the Devil's Tritone.
People go crazy for it.
- [Joel] Is this
bugging you guys?
I mean just let me know
if it's bugging you.
Tends to annoy some people
sometimes and I find that I...
I don't know.
Is that bugging you?
- I said cool it!
- [Servo] I don't know that one,
but this one's called
Put a Sock In It.
- I think it's best
if you both cooled it.
- He's making me nervous
with that git fiddle.
- Sit down.
- [Crow] I mean, it's
pretty and all but quit it.
- Sit down.
- [Joel] Hey, get that
shotgun to sing a song.
- [Jeeter] Can the music?
- [Crow] Canned music?
No way, I'm an
artist, I have values!
- Thank you.
Look, cats.
Now that we got our arsenal,
it's gonna be Kicksville
from here on out.
- [Crow] I'm being
transferred to Kicksville?
- Go get me those
layouts you drew up.
- [Joel] On the laser printer.
Ouch, owie.
Too tight.
(Crow mimics squeaking)
(Joel sneezes)
- [Joel] Excuse me.
- [Crow] Gesundheit.
- [Joel] There's Don
Ho's jacket up there.
- [Servo] Let's see: "We
hold these truths to..."
Wait a minute, this isn't right.
- When you guys
have been takin' in
all that sack time
in the afternoon.
- [Crow] I've been taking
a correspondence course.
- I've had our little
actress here out performing.
She cased some pads that
are filled with more bread
than you ever dreamed existed.
- [Servo] Whoa, that's a
lotta slang for one sentence.
- You're outta sight, baby.
- [Joel] Well you better
put your bifocals in.
- Real, real righteous.
(Servo mimics deep kissing)
- [Crow] Banjo, I
believe you're next.
Fatty, wait your turn.
- Now if my little flock
will gather round...
(Crow and Servo mimic sheep)
- [Joel] Will I ever be
as smart as that guy?
I just don't think so.
I don't think I'll do it.
- [Crow] Boss,
I made some bars but I can't
get the oven to preheat.
Can you help me?
- He's outta sight, baby.
He's okay.
- Why take a chance?
- [Servo] He's in
plain sight, I think.
- We can brief him
on the way tomorrow.
He's only the driver.
- Rod.
- [Servo] Rod,
we need a few more people
nibbling on me here.
Come on over.
- Go out and serenade the moon.
- [Joel] Wear a necktie
so I know it's you.
- What's the matter,
don't you trust me?
- Let's just say...
- [All] No.
- Security precautions.
- [Crow] Okay,
security precautions.
Give us another one, that's fun.
- Okay, it's your race.
- [Joel] White Nazi race.
- But if I'm gonna
be the driver,
you're gonna have to
tell me what's happening.
- [Joel] Well there's a
steering wheel and a pedal...
Oh, would you just
get out of here!
Crazy kooky-head.
- That square bugs me!
He really bugs me!
- [Crow] We're here,
man, let it out.
- Don't let him bug ya, baby.
- [Crow] See this
shoulder, it's here for ya.
- For a while.
- [Joel] Eat. Eat, Fatty.
- Go outside and
keep your eye on him.
- [Servo] Which one?
(laughs goofily)
- No, Fats.
On second thought,
Linda, you go out and watch him.
It won't be so obvious, baby.
- Just let me comb my hair
and I'll be on him
like a bloodhound.
(Crow and Servo howl)
- [Joel] Aqualung!
- [Crow] Freebird!
- [Joel] Hey,
that's a pretty good
G. Gordon Liddy
impression there.
- [Servo] Meanwhile,
in Africa...
- [Joel] Let's see,
if you are not wearing
any underwear, smile.
- [Crow] Underwear?
- [Servo] Note to
myself: get new agent.
Thank you.
- [Joel] What's he gonna do?
- [Crow] Fold it so
no one can read it.
- [Servo] And then...
Huh?
- [Crow] Oh, he's sending
it by carrier vole.
- [Joel] I've...
hidden... the note.
- [Servo] We'll be back with
Peek-a-Boo Siding Showcase
but first (chuckles)
a little of her.
- [Servo] Quick.
- [Crow] Think fast.
This'll fool her.
(chuckles)
- There's the signal now.
Run up and get the message.
- [Servo] Ooh, but it
might be dangerous!
- [Joel] Ouch. Sting-y.
- [Crow] She must go
through a lot of pants.
(Joel mimics squeaking)
- Hold it. Hold it, Bob.
- [Crow] Hold what?
- [Servo] Now hold
it up to the light.
- Looks like Rod's got company.
- [Crow] Uh oh.
Love me tender, love me sweet.
Thank you very much.
Elvis has left the theater.
- [Joel] He's sending
another message now.
- [Servo] It's a
musical message of love.
- You're quite the
troubadour, aren't you?
- [Joel] Yeah, and
I play guitar too!
- Just a roving minstrel
at your service, me lady.
- Play on.
- [Crow] McDuff.
- What would you like to hear?
- [Linda] Whatever
strikes your fancy.
- [Servo] Personally, I
like guys in clown suits.
(Rod plays guitar)
- [Joel] Oh, the
Wango Ze Tango, huh?
- [Servo] Nothing like
a moonlit afternoon.
(all sing like Jerry Lewis)
♪ 'Cause I like what I know ♪
♪ About you ♪
- [Joel] What a jerk.
- [Crow] Looks like
Frank Sinatra, Jr.
(horn plays)
Thank you, brother
squirrel, for the horn.
- [Joel] Special music by
the Ant Farm Family Singers.
- [Servo] Good thing
the Nelson Riddle gang
is in the next cottage.
- [Crow] Maybe I can kill
him with a cigarette.
- [Joel] Do some backup.
(Servo scats bass)
♪ But I still know nothing ♪
- [Crow] Take it, chipmunks!
♪ About your secret charm ♪
- [Joel] (sighs) I hope
this isn't a long song.
♪ 'Cause I've never kissed you ♪
- [Crow] This is a cover of
an old Kristie Weasel song.
- [Joel] New Kristie Weasels?
- [Crow] Yep.
- [Servo] I thought it
was Up with Weasels.
You talkin' to me?
♪ One night I will ♪
(Servo swoons)
- [Servo] Carried away.
- [Crow] My god, are you okay?
- [Servo] Little
B.J. Thomas there.
♪ Then I love ♪
♪ What I know ♪
- [Servo] A little
flat there, squirrels.
♪ About ♪
♪ You ♪
- [Crow] This must be
the B side of the 45.
Next, thank you!
We'll call you.
- You're out of sight, baby.
Real righteous.
- [Joel] What does that mean?
- [Crow] I don't know.
- Thank you, I'm flattered.
- [Crow] I think.
- Tell me something, Linda.
- Sure, what do
you want to know?
- [Servo] Does light stand still
on the edge of a black hole?
- What's your game?
Why do you hang around with
guys like Jeeter and Banjo for?
- They're the greatest.
With them, everything's cool.
Never a dull moment.
- [Crow] Yeah, just like
the Algonquin Round Table.
- What are you looking for?
The high living, the sports car?
(Linda laughs)
- You're not a very good
judge of character, are you?
- [Servo] Nope.
- You're square, baby.
So square you look like a box.
- [Joel] Yeah, but
there's a prize inside.
Ho!
- Well then why?
- The kicks, baby, the kicks.
- [Servo] The cereal?
- [Joel] Yeah, kids like
Kix for what Kix has got!
Moms like Kix for
what Kix is not!
- You're flirting with death.
- [Crow] Speech! Speech!
- You feel alive.
You feel like...
Like it's great to
be young, to be free.
No ring on your finger.
- [Servo] No bell on your toe.
- No snotty-nosed brats.
- [Joel] You make
it sound so good!
- Just you, alive!
- A bike and a robbery
aren't the same thing.
- [Servo] Oh, shut up, shut up!
- You get your kicks
from that guitar.
From singing.
- [Joel] Yeah, why?
- You used to get
them from having
400 horses in front of you
and death staring
you in the face.
- [Crow] Yeah, but that's
when he was in Ben Hur.
- Still not the same thing.
- Oh yes it is, it's the same.
When you look death in the face,
whether it's from
behind the wheel
or looking at a
policeman's gun...
- [Joel] Or in the mirror.
- I don't dig you.
- Do you dig this?
- [Servo] Well, I don't
know-- (muffled slurping)
- Are you looking for trouble?
- [Servo] Well you won't
find it in my dental work.
- Just for kicks.
- [Joel] Silly Rabbi,
kicks are for Trids!
(Servo slurping)
- [Crow] Is that the signal?
- [Servo] Well, at least
her three boyfriends
aren't homicidal and looking
for something like this.
- [Joel] You taste
like wet leaves.
- [Crow] Their love
can be dry cleaned.
- [Servo] Now what
do you mean by "mmm"?
- [Joel] I'd like to ask her out
but I'm afraid of rejection.
- [Crow] They're neat.
- [Linda] Oh...
- [Joel] What does "oh" mean?
(musical sting)
- [All] Huh?
- [Linda] Banjo!
- [Crow] No, Stiletto.
- Man, you're messing
with private stock.
- [Servo] Okay, now what
the hell did he say?
I haven't understood
a word this guy said!
- [Linda] No!
- [Crow] Uh oh.
- [Servo] Ooh, that had to hurt.
- [Joel] Banjo,
you're just too high strung.
- [Servo] Banjo
and guitar together
and they're dueling.
- [Joel] Now the guitar's gonna
beat the banjo every time.
- Stop him, he's gonna kill him!
- [Crow] Maybe
that's a good thing.
(Joel and bots groan)
- [Joel] They're rough.
- [Servo] Looks like Banjo's
a little out of tune there.
(grunts)
- [Joel] Yeah,
tell your friends.
Oh, they're here.
- [Crow] Eat it, boy, eat it!
- Hey! Cut it!
Then bathe in my blood.
- Kill him, baby!
Kill him!
Kill him off!
He's a loser, baby!
- Ah, he's not worth killing.
- [Servo] Not worth killing?
Don't you ever say that!
- I assume we're gettin' up
early tomorrow.
Think I'll call it a night.
- [Joel] Or an
afternoon or whatever.
I can't tell by the light.
(Joel laughs goofily)
Here's your guitar, man.
- [Crow] Thank you,
thank you very much.
I think I'm gonna go
write a song about this.
- What was that all about?
- [Servo] He kicked my butt.
Weren't you there?
- Well, baby.
Did you enjoy it?
- So you want me to vomit
every time another
man comes around?
- [Joel] Well you do
when I come around.
- You don't mix
business with pleasure!
I thought you were
supposed to be tough.
Next time, act it!
- [Servo] I hate getting notes
right after the performance.
- Children, we got
a busy day tomorrow.
Let's get some sleep.
- [Crow] Yeah, come
on, we got early mass.
Oh, the shame! The shame!
Oh, the pain and shame!
- [Joel] I'm wigging!
- [Servo] Whoa.
Meanwhile, Napoleon
Solo is in Hungary.
Open Channel B.
- [Joel] Gotta shake the dew
off the old helmet there.
- [Crow] Thank you, magic
night vision binoculars.
- [Joel] I gotta tinky.
- [Servo] I gotta...
(clears throat)
Oh, I gotta go see
a man about a horse.
- [Crow] (groans) What a day.
It's great.
Better lock up.
A lotta creeps around here.
- [Joel] Thanks for the
groovy charts, Mr. Squirrel,
wherever you are.
- [Servo] Heavy, guys.
Love their station wagon.
- [Crow] Okay now, everybody in?
Buckle up!
- [Joel] Hey, how
would you like someone
putting a cigarette out on you!
- [Crow] Killer spleef, man.
- [Joel] Figurines,
the diet crunch.
- [Crow] Hey, there's
something about that guy
that just screams "I'm
not really a cop".
- [Servo] Let's
see what it says.
It says,
"Put me back, you idiot."
Hey, I gotta go tell a tree!
- Three-12 to 5-0-7.
Three-12 to 5-O-7.
- [Joel] (panting) We were
in the car the whole time!
We weren't doing anything!
- Three-12, I read
you, go ahead, okay?
- Suspects just drove off
from house in gray wagon.
- Thanks, Ben, we'll
take it from here.
Okay, Charlie, let's go.
- [Servo] Bye bye.
- [Crow] Hey, but
we're on break!
- [Servo] Not any more.
- [Crow] Darn.
- Now Rod, baby,
here's the scene.
As you can see...
- [Servo] Scene 35.
- [Jeeter] Orange
goes to the right,
grapefruit goes to the left.
Now what does that spell?
- [Servo] Fruit salad!
- You're the riddler, what?
(Crow laughs like The Riddler)
- Lots of bread.
- So what are we gonna do,
stop and pick an orange?
(Joel laughs mockingly)
- [Joel] This guy's
crazy, cracks me up!
- You're really righteous,
baby, really righteous.
I really dig him.
- So I cracked a funny.
- [Crow] And you've
got a funny crack.
- [Servo] Polish that
up, will ya, Joel?
(Joel hums)
- It has this little old bank
that's just loaded with bread.
- [Servo] I don't know,
but I think you're
talking about a bakery.
- And it's just waiting for
the five of us to slice it up.
- [Servo] Good job.
- Sounds easy.
How do we work it?
- Well, Linda baby being the
best little actress I know...
- [Crow] Except for Streep.
- Will make everything
easy for us.
You wait in the car,
be ready to move.
- [Servo] The car?
- We'll just go in
and help ourselves
to all of that wonderful bread.
- There's somethin'
comin' up behind us, man.
- [Crow] That's
the sun, you idiot!
It happens every
day at this time.
- Better play it cool, Rod,
and slow down and
see if they pass us.
- [Joel] It's Spiro Agnew...
And Spiro Agnew in
The Parent Trap!
- [Servo] (laughs) Good one.
- 5-O-7 to all units.
5-O-7 to all units.
Plan R, that is, Plan
Robert is now in effect.
(Joel mimics punching bag)
- [Servo] That's R for
rump, we're gonna moon him.
Okay, drop trow there, Bob.
- [Joel] Those guys mooned us!
- Smell like fuzz, man.
- [Joel] Oh, that's just me.
- For the first time
in your life, Banjo,
I think you're right.
- [Crow] Looks like
they're in a car wash.
- Jeeter, if it is the
man, what do we do?
- Just play it cool, baby.
We'll just play it cool.
- [Crow] Yeah, hit
the AC, play it cool.
- We'll follow them for a
while and see what happens.
- What do we do now, Lieutenant?
- [Servo] We can enter
a Biggest Ear contest.
He wins.
- Go ahead and turn off
into that side road.
- [Joel] We'll pick up some
jams, jellies, some compotes.
They look like they got
some nice corn on the cob
up this end of the woods.
- [Servo] Scones, cucumbers.
Crenshaws.
- Okay, now what?
- My guess is that
the fuzz is staked out
all along the main highway
between here and Citrusville.
- [Crow] All both of them.
- They report our position
as we passed them.
- Look, aren't you
jumpin' to conclusions?
Because two men
passed us in a car...
- [Servo] Whoa, whoa, brake!
- That doesn't mean
we're bein' followed.
- [Joel] Oh, it's
just the camera moved.
- For all we know, you may
be workin' with the fuzz.
- Cool it, Banjo.
Cool it.
Rod's been with us every
minute of the time.
How could he contact the
cops, by carrier pigeon?
- [Servo] No, by carrier vole.
- What now, daddy?
- [Joel] This is
a map of London.
- We can't go cross-country...
- [Crow] And we
can't go straight up.
Remember when we tried that?
- We could only get to about
maybe two miles of Citrusville.
Then we'd be spotted.
- Hey.
Why don't you forget the bank?
Forget everything, man!
Let's go home.
- You forgot the name
of the game, Rod.
- [Servo] What's that?
- It's kicks.
- [Joel] Oh, would you
shut up about the kicks!
- You didn't learn a
thing last night, did you?
- [Joel] Well I did,
but I don't think we could
use it to rob a bank.
- Through and through!
- No physical violence, please.
- [Servo] Mental violence.
- Let's just be one
big happy family.
- [Crow] Yeah, the Mansons.
(mimics train whistle)
- [Joel] Huh? What
is it little fella?
You workin' on your
doctorate over there?
What a train?
In Dead Rock Canyon, huh?
- Fats, baby, I love ya!
- [Crow] You finally figured
out positive ion bonding!
- Simply brilliant!
- What's he sayin'?
- The railroad tracks.
Cross the railroad tracks.
- [Servo] Yeah, railroad tracks!
Oh, the railroad tracks!
Hey, there's a highway right
next to the railroad tracks.
They'll never find them there!
- [Joel] Hey, I hear a big,
stupid ending coming, you guys.
- [Crow] Citrusville,
city of progress.
Where everyone is juice!
- [Joel] Citrusville,
a great place to
get some orange juice.
- [Servo] Boy, I
bet they could score
80 to a hundred
bucks in this town.
- [Joel] At least they haven't
broken any traffic laws.
- [Crow] That's good.
If they're able to pull off
the robbery and kill somebody,
I hope they at
least get gas money.
- [All] Let's go to Juice Land!
Let's go to Juice Land!
- [Joel] Hey, look,
you kids be quiet
or I'm gonna turn
this car around!
- Okay, baby.
We'll once it around the block.
That'll be your time
to look things over.
- [Servo] I've just
seen the whole town.
- [Joel] You know, (sniffs)
these guys just plain smell.
B.O., big time.
Icky.
- [Crow] Cute.
Four, five, dollars.
You've broken the bank!
- Thank you.
- Okay, see you tomorrow.
- [Servo] It's always a pleasure
to do service with
our largest depositor.
- [Joel] Ms. Hathaway, Mr.
Drysdale's been looking for you.
- Four-86.
- [Servo] Four-86, that what
they've got in the vault.
- [Crow] That's what
they're insured to.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, may I help you?
- Yes, I'd like $500...
- [Joel] Oh, dream on, lady!
- Tens, twenties, or fifties?
- Fifties would be fine.
- [Crow] With your
blood on them.
Hey, I found a five
under this drawer!
We could stay open!
- [Servo] Let's split, guys.
- [Joel] Oh, yeah.
- Fill in your name and address.
- [Joel] We'll gonna
have to mail the money
to you in six weeks.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
(Servo humming)
- I had no idea Gypsy had
such a powerful brain.
Running all the
working functions
of the Satellite of
Love and everything.
I even found out she
re-analogued my brain
when I had that computer virus.
- Yep.
Joel must have not
told us for a reason.
You know it's funny
how working outdoors
makes you feel comfortable
pondering such questions.
- Yeah, I was gonna
say how nice it was
not always having to
talk when we're together.
- Yeah, that's neat.
- Oh, here they come!
Servo, do that cricket
noise you do so well
and I'll run lights, okay?
(Servo chirps)
- Oh, for fun, yeah.
I know exactly how it is.
You know, we're pretty
much the same that way.
You just gotta let off
steam sometimes, you know.
This looks like a nice
place to rest, doesn't it?
- It sure does, Joel.
You know, Joel...
- What?
- I feel so special.
- Uh-huh, good, okay.
Hey, Cambot, I hope
you're getting this.
We'll want to use this in
Gypsy's scrapbook later.
Anyway,
I'm just a wandering minstrel
at your service, my lady.
- Play on, my liege.
♪ I know what I like ♪
♪ And I like what I know ♪
♪ 'Cause I know ♪
♪ What I like ♪
♪ About you ♪
You know, I feel kinda like
Mac Davis on The Muppet Show.
♪ I know all your ways ♪
- My ways.
♪ And your ways please me so ♪
- So so.
♪ 'Cause I like what I know ♪
♪ About you ♪
- Oh, Joel, hold me!
- Man, you messin'
with private stock!
- Let's get him!
(yelling)
- I'm in it for the kicks.
- [Joel] I'm glad we
cheered her up anyway.
- [Servo] Sorry about
beating you up and all.
- [Joel] That's okay.
You guys look cute
in those outfits.
(all slurp)
- [Servo] Wait, what?
She's gonna hold the
place up with a syringe?
- [Crow] Anybody
move, I get high.
- [Joel] Oh, look.
It's Scruffy the
lovable cop clown.
Jimmy hat.
- Okay, baby.
Everything's set, let's move it!
- [Servo] He must be psychic.
- [Linda] The guard's
out of the way.
- [Crow] What do you mean?
He's in the middle of the floor!
- Move! I said move!
Fats, fill them bags!
You, blondie, over here!
- [Servo] What is he
speaking in Sanskrit?
Slow down!
- Fats, you and Linda
go get the money!
- [Crow] It's code.
- [Joel] I want firm tummies
and a nice straight dance line.
Come on!
- [Crow] Oh, great.
There's stamps and
some paperclips
and Garfield sticker and hey,
grab that statue that says
World's Greatest Grandma!
- [Servo] Hey look, ten dollars!
We're set for the
rest of our lives
unless we wanna buy a
12-pack or somethin'.
- [Crow] Hey, they play
the Ventures at this bank.
- [Joel] They got everything.
Stadium blanket, calendar,
Lincoln coin bank!
- [Servo] Look at the bank sign.
It's printed with electrician's
tape on ceiling tile.
- [Crow] Thinking of growing
a Van Dyke, what do ya think?
- [Joel] Did you see
Cop Rock last night?
It sucked.
- [Servo] Hmm...
Now, if I could just remember
by Aldis code from the Navy.
- Look at the lights!
- [Servo] What about 'em?
- [Joel] Whoa.
You're bright!
- [Servo] Hey, man,
he's doin' Aldis code!
(all whispering "help")
- Looks like he's
trying to signal us.
- [Joel] Oh, no, he's
just testin' his lights.
Let's go dunk a couple
of spud nuts, eh, Phil?
(rapid tapping)
- [Crow] Hey, is that their car?
Sounds like they
got a tappet loose.
(muffled tapping)
That's better.
- [Servo] What's all this then?
I mean, what's
goin' on here, boy?
- Well, son, what's
the lights for?
- [Joel] Illuminating
the road after dark, sir?
- There's three men and
a girl robbin' that bank.
- [All] And a baby.
- Jeeter!
It's the Gestapo and they're
talkin' to Rod, let's split!
- [Crow] No, you're the Gestapo.
- Linda, Fats!
Grab that loot, let's go!
- This better not be a joke.
- [Servo] Well, it is a
joke, but it's still true.
- Stay put, kid.
- [Servo] Here we go.
- [Joel] That's a
nice wide spread.
He must have had a
modified choke on that.
- Banjo just hit a
couple of the fuzz!
- [All] What?
- Hold it, creep!
Or I'll blow your brains out!
- Come on, move!
Linda, hurry up!
- [Crow] In these
heels? Are you crazy?
- [Joel] Okay, comin' boss.
- [Crow] Nice tag.
(bell rings)
- [Servo] School's
out! Recess, everybody!
- [Crow] Okay, now we all
saw the Zupruder film.
You be Kennedy! (laughs)
- [Banjo] He signaled the man!
- [Jeeter] Banjo,
get in the car.
Banjo, get in the car!
- [All] What?
- That wasn't a very
nice thing to do.
- If Banjo's telling the truth,
why don't we just dump him now?
- Because this creep is gonna
get us away from little men.
He's gonna drive the
race of his life.
Put your foot to
the floorboard, man.
Move it!
I said move it!
- [Joel] But remember
your seatbelt.
Check your blind spot.
Three point check!
That's better.
- [Servo] No, not this way, man!
My mom will see me! Oh!
- [Jeeter] Come on,
man, earn your money!
Faster! Faster!
- [Crow] Oh, you poor officer!
Can I get you a donut?
- [Joel] (grunting)
Your knee on my chest!
- [Servo] I'm sorry
but you're dead.
No donuts.
- [Joel] Poor guy.
- Mayday, mayday.
- [Crow] He used to be a pilot.
- [Servo] I used too much rouge!
- ...just robbed the
Citrusville bank.
- 5-O-7 to all units.
5-O-7 to all units.
Whatever your location,
proceed to roadblock
stations around Citrusville.
- [Joel] Uh, we are
all the units, sir.
- ...proceed to roadblock
stations around Citrusville.
- [Crow] Ha! They're gonna
put the squeeze on 'em in
Citrusville! (laughs)
- [Servo] Nelson Riddle
and his orchestra!
- [Crow] Squeeze on
'em, see, 'cause--
- [Servo] Yeah, we got it, Crow.
- [Crow] What's Citrusville
famous for, you suppose?
- [Servo] Probably
dairy products.
- [Crow] I... huh?
- [Joel] Police cars
courtesy of Grandma.
- [Jeeter] You're
doing great, baby.
- [Crow] Don't call
me that at work.
- Hey, that looks
like their car!
- [Servo] Naw!
Couldn't be, they're miles away.
(gunshots fire)
(Banjo yells)
- [Servo] That'll teach him.
- [Crow] Calgon, take me away!
- [Joel] I got one
in my hair! Crawlers!
- [Servo] Stupid old bun!
- Another one for me.
- [Joel] You know, this
really is kinda fun!
I'm having a really good time!
- [Crow] I'll get a
Kleenex, Bob. Stay there.
- [Servo] Officer
down, officer down.
I need bear claws...
I mean, backup, send
a jelly donut...
I mean, send help.
- [Cop] Gang headed
east on Old Citrus Road.
Just killed my partner.
- [Joel] And I'm all
busted up inside, over.
- [Banjo] Here comes the fuzz!
- [All] Here comes the
fuzz! Here comes the fuzz!
Fuzz is comin'!
(siren blares)
- [Servo] He's
doing really well.
- [Crow] Yeah, this is
the longest he's driven
without rolling and burning.
- [Banjo] Another roadblock!
- [Jeeter] Drive through
it, man, drive through it!
- [Servo] Whoa!
- [Joel] You know, we
really should have blocked
the other road, too.
What were we thinking?
- [Crow] Roadblock detour.
- [Banjo] Down the
Yellow Brick Road, man!
- [Servo] Guess we're not
in Kansas anymore, dude!
Go kill Dorothy.
- [Crow] That's kind of
like closing the barn door
after the cows are out.
Come on, dummy.
- [Joel] Signal
your turn, please.
Oh well.
- [Crow] What's he gonna
do, shoot at oranges?
- [Servo] Looks like it.
(gunshots fire)
(siren blares)
(tires screech)
- [Servo] Oh, now, that's
a fire siren. Come on!
(gunshot fires)
- [Joel] I'm huge! I'm immense!
- [Crow] Hey,
look, Erik Estrada!
- [Jeeter] Slow 'em down, Banjo!
(gunshot fires)
Two barrels for
Banjo, comin' up!
- [Servo] Did he say
"two bowels for Banjo"?
- [Joel] Bedtime for Banjo?
- [Crow] Would you
get your arms and legs
inside this car, please?
- [Joel] How am I
doin' it? I don't know!
- [Banjo] Man, we rollin'!
- [Joel] You wanna
get some waggits
and some rolls
and some reezen-rozzen.
(Servo laughs gravelly)
Everyday!
All along the way.
- [Crow] By this time,
the old Duke boys had killed
just about every cop in town.
And Daisy had slipped into
somethin' more comfortable.
(tires screech)
- [Servo] Oh, it's
a squealing swamp.
Oh, there's the exploding bush.
- [Jeeter] Earn your money!
Drive, baby, drive!
- [Crow] What do you
think I'm doing?!
Oh, look, I'm cranky
and hungry, I'm sorry.
- [Joel] Back into
the squealing swamp.
- [Servo] So this is the
point where the director said,
"Use everything we shot."
- What's wrong with the car?
- [Joel] Who's talking?
- They musta hit the gas tank.
- [Servo] I dunno.
- [Jeeter] See the
lighthouse? Stop there.
- [Servo] Lighthouse?
They're in the woods!
- [Crow] Going down.
We've lost an engine.
(siren blares)
(gunshot fires)
- [Servo] Lighthouse?
- [Joel] Oh, it's
for Winnebagos.
- [Crow] Well, it's
up to the Navy now.
It's out of our jurisdiction.
- Come on baby, let's go!
- [Joel] Whoa! That's too close.
Stop calling me baby.
- [Crow] Oh, great hideout.
If they have to
spend any time there,
they can eat the
bricks, I guess.
- [Joel] Oh, look, they're
in a nautilus, you guys.
- [Servo] It's like
the Time Tunnel.
- [Crow] Don't shoot
the car, we need that!
- [Servo] Oh, sorry!
Accidentally shot a cop, sorry.
- [Jeeter] Load it up, Linda.
It's just like shooting
ducks in an alley.
- [Joel] I think it's
fish in a barrel,
but I know what you mean,
and you'll know what
we mean after this.
- [Servo] For the glory
of the SLA, Tanya.
- [Joel] I just got a thing
about girls with guns, I dunno.
(gunshots fire)
- [Servo] Hi.
- [Crow] Here you go, Hoss.
Nice shootin', Little Joe!
My hair's stuck!
- [Joel] I'm old enough
to drive and drink
but not be in a war.
What do you think?
- [Servo] Hey, it's Diana Rigg.
- [Crow] Join us!
- [Servo] Gettin'
enough kicks now, baby?
Yeah.
Look, you got somethin'
to say, say it.
- [Joel] You killed
a tree, Banjo!
- [Crow] Oh, oh-oh, oh-oh!
Excuse me!
- [Banjo] I got me one!
I got me a man!
- [Servo] I'm happy for
ya, now go shoot cops.
- [Joel] Quite a dance move.
- [Servo] Oh! My head's
tryin' to blow up!
- I can't make it here,
man! I can't make it!
- [Joel] He's wigging!
Banjo, don't be a hero!
- [Servo] Come back, Banjo!
Stupid old gun!
- Cover him, Fats, cover him!
- [Servo] Now, wait a minute.
Banjo's about two feet
away, look at that.
Two feet away from the cops.
Criminy.
- [Joel] He's over there, yeah.
- [Servo] Uh oh.
- [Joel] That's pretty good
with a shotgun at that distance.
- [Crow] Must be
using a full choke.
- The lousy men got him.
They got Banjo!
- [Joel] They torched
his bike, too.
- Grab the rifle.
Go upstairs as fast as you can.
See if you can pick off
any of them from upstairs.
- [Crow] O-thay.
I'll be running up there now.
(Crow panting)
- [Servo] Long way up.
- [Servo] Oh! They
got my foot, Charlie!
They got my foot.
- [Crow] Hey, it's
a double helix.
- [Servo] Thank you for
the Crick and Watson joke.
- [Joel] You know, he's
kind of an easy target.
Fat, drunk and
stupid, I wonder...
- [Crow] He could
never hit him though.
- [Servo] One if by
land, two if by stupid.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Hey, I've always
wanted that cool lid.
- [Servo] Philip Glass music!
- [Joel] I always thought
only the good died young.
- [Servo] Live fast, die young,
and leave a fat,
bloated, ugly corpse.
(gunshots fire)
Here we go again with him.
- [Crow] Uh oh.
- Fats!
Fats, he's comin' your way!
Kill him! Kill him!
Hand me the shotgun!
- [Servo] Quick.
(Servo panting)
- [Crow] Oh, I
gotta quit smokin'.
(Servo panting)
(jazzy beat)
(Servo scats)
- [Servo] Now,
now wait a minute!
Just, just wait a minute here!
- [Joel] I will kill you!
- [Crow] I'm gettin' dizzy.
- [Servo] Me too.
(gunshot fires)
- [Joel] Hey, that's
not completely fair!
- [Crow] Hey, mister,
can you help me?
I need so--
- [Servo] You know in
a more expensive movie,
they would have tossed him over.
- [Joel] Or at least used
him as a shield or something.
- [Crow] It's filled with Pez!
- [Servo] He's upstairs.
Thanks, Fats.
You know, you're smarter dead.
Sounds like Johnny Cash music.
- [Crow] Kill, kill, kill.
Die, die, die!
When will it end?!
- [Servo] I dunno.
- [Joel] Oh, man, you
got my windbreaker!
This is a Members Only,
too, it's not cheap!
Oh, I'm no good at
anything, I'm terrible.
I can't drive, can't shoot.
What the hell am I good at?!
Oh, jeepers, I'll never
get in another movie.
- [Servo] At least
the music's gone.
Ow!
- Well if it isn't Rod.
- [Servo] What?
- [Crow] Uh oh.
- [Servo] Yeah, he's
gettin' serious.
He took his sunglasses off.
Whoa!
- [Crow] Servo, save yourself!
Get outta the way!
(Jeeter laughs)
- See ya later.
- [Servo] Alligator.
Not!
(gunshot fires)
- [Joel] What gives?
(Jeeter screams)
Oh, he's all bendy
and floppy and stuff.
- [Crow] That was kinda neat.
(Servo laughs)
- [Servo] Sorry.
- [Joel] Heavy.
- [Servo] It kinda looks like
the beginning of a Bond film,
doesn't it?
- [Crow] Hey, there's the girl
with the golden gun! (laughs)
(Servo sighs)
- [Joel] It's been a big day.
- [Servo] I'm just not
havin' a good week.
Here.
A gift for you.
- [Crow] I didn't
get you anything.
- Kicks, baby.
- [Joel] They're not for Trids.
- Kicks.
It was the wildest.
- [Servo] Kicks just keep
getting harder to find.
- [Crow] Ew!
You still taste like
Fatty, don't you brush?
- [Servo] Oh, she's crying.
- Charlie, go on
up and check Fats.
Take her away, Bob.
- [Servo] Are there
kicks in prison, honey?
- [Joel] I'm here, Bob.
♪ I know ♪
- [Servo] Here we go again.
♪ All your ways ♪
- [Joel] You know,
I love that song.
And I like your
Ralston-Purina suit, too.
- [Crow] Check.
Hey! It's God-cam.
♪ I like ♪
♪ What I know ♪
♪ About you ♪
- [Joel] I see.
(Servo swoons)
- [Joel] You know,
I'm gonna miss her and
all her murderous ways.
- [Crow] She was neat.
- [Servo] In a sick sort of way.
Well, Rod, 13 dead cops,
six dead innocent bystanders,
a couple of dead bikers.
Good work!
I'd like to have you on
my team again sometime.
What do you think?
- [Joel] Signal the God-cam.
- [Crow] 'Cause I
get a kick outta...
Oh, wrong song, sorry. (laughs)
- [Servo] Louie,
this could be the start
of a beautiful friendship.
- [Joel] Man, when you
were trying to signal me,
that was so funny.
I thought you were
kissing the girl.
I thought that was
the sign... oh, boy.
Well we can laugh
about it now but...
Whatcha doin' now?
- [Crow] Do you live alone?
Would you like to?
- [Servo] I've had enough.
Let's get outta here.
- [Joel] We should really go.
Come on.
(grunting) You're getting
heavy, you know that?
You know, guys, I feel
great, I'm flyin' high!
- Huh?
- Joel, how can you feel good
after that kidney
stone of a movie?
- Yeah, I'm downright depressed.
If I had wrists, I'd contemplate
slitting them right now.
- What, huh?
- This movie!
It was like spending the
weekend with your dentist!
- Oh you guys, listen.
You gotta take it easier,
it's just a movie.
Yes, it was like being pulled
through a dark, tarry abyss,
but it's only a movie.
You gotta use your intelligence
to abstract yourself
from the pain.
You know, like,
yeah, the writer
was only interested
in shallow stereotypes
of mid-'60s sociopaths.
You just gotta deal with it.
- Oh, I see.
The villains were so
cliched, they were laughable!
(laughs)
- Right! That's it exactly.
- And the hero was such a wimp,
his only heroic act was
to flash his headlights.
That's funny!
(laughs)
- Yeah, you guys.
Keep in mind this is
during the Otto Preminger
time of film.
You know, like anti-hero,
plots that didn't go anywhere,
that kinda thing.
- So the hero was supposed to
be unattractive and spineless.
- Exactly! Now you're
surfing on my wave.
Take it, Tom Servo.
- Oh, um, well,
even though this was
one of the ugliest
extended families
in movie history,
they drove one of the finest
station wagons on the market!
- Hey! That was hysterical!
- You know, you're right, Joel.
Looking at the movie your
way makes me feel great!
- Yeah, I really like
this wild rebel thing!
Yahoo!
- What the hell is
going on up there?
- Really, I thought this
film was supposed to be
an emotional kneecapping
for you guys.
(dance music)
(Crow cheering)
- I don't believe it, Frank!
This film had absolutely
nothing going for it!
- An ugly cast
and an ugly script
doing really stupid, uh...
(chuckles)
I mean, wait a minute,
think about it though.
The Citrusville National Bank.
The hypodermic needle
putting the guard out.
I mean it was so stupid,
it was kind of funny.
It had wit, it had charm,
it was quirky, it was offbeat.
I'm gonna give this one my
highest rating: five skulls.
Woo!
- I really thought we
had you this time, Joely.
Don't you have a letter
to read or something?
(dance music, cheering)
- All right, all right, okay.
Back it off, you guys!
Cut it out, cut the
music, all right.
All right, we gotta
read a letter, you guys.
- [Servo] Oh, letters! Great!
- Yeah, this is an
interesting one.
It says, "Dear Joel, I
am in fact a scientist."
(balloon pops)
Excuse me.
"I am a PhD immunologist.
"I work a the Pittsburgh
Cancer Institute
"and study natural killer cells.
"What a great term that would be
"in a science fiction
movie," she writes.
"Perhaps my background gives
me a particular framework,
"but I am a devoted
MST 3000 fan.
"The letters you read each
week are still from children.
"I guess a letter from
a 30-year-old scientist
"without any drawings
doesn't have a prayer
"in making it on the air,
"so perhaps I should
come up with a drawing."
That's from Rebecca
P. Schell, PhD.
And here's the
drawing right there.
Let's get that on still
store there, Cambot.
- [Servo] Not bad for
a 30-year-old, huh?
- It says "Who will win?"
The Natural Killer
Cell or Tom Servo?
Hey, give us some more
music there, Cambot!
(dance music, cheering)
Okay, we'll see you later!
We're having a great time!
Wish you were here, scientists!
- No no no no,
you win this time.
As for me,
I've gotta put Frank
down for the night.
Until next time.
(Frank yells)
("The Love Theme from Mystery
Science Theater 3000")